

Francesca Kirby

Dedicated and results-d riven personal trainer with 8+ years' experience supporting clients to meet their fitness goals in commercial gyms. Clear and effective communication style and ability to build positive long-term relationships with customers. Detailed specialist knowledge of fitness and nutrition to manage diabetes and cardiovascular conditions. Qualified to lead group yoga sessions.

Professional Experience

Personal Trainer

Bounce Fitness. San Francisco, CA August 2018 - Present

- Carry out detailed consultations and movement assessments to onboard new clients
- Respond to client's unique requirements and goals to create individual training and nutrition plans
- Del i ver on e-o n-on e a nd grou p f i tness session s to six c l ients per day usi n g a ra n ge
 of training styles and equipment
- Provide spec i al ized s u ppo rt for c I i e nts wi th spec i fic h ea 1th con d it io n s to allow them to access fitness activities safely

Personal Trainer

Fitness SF, San Francisco. CA January 2013 - August 2018

- Led bi-weekly group yoga classes, including prenatal yoga, to improve clients' strength, flexibility, and general well-being
- Kept a safe and clean working area, ensuring all equipment remained in good working order
- Created and delivered a 12-week weight loss challenge to attract new clients to the gym, resulting in an 80% adherence

III My Road, San Francisco, CA 66778 f ki rby@myema i I .co m (111)222-3333

Education

Bachelor of Science in Kinesiology

San Francisco State University, San Francisco, CA September 2008 - August 2012

Key Skills

- Thorough understanding of safeguarding and health and safety best practices in commercial gyms
- Stron g verba I a n d written communication skills
- Warm and encouraging coaching style
- Able to manage challenging workloads with large client lists
- Adept at creating personalized plans considering dietary and physical restrictions

Certifications

- Personal Trainer Certification,
 American Council on Exercise, 2013
- Yoga All iance Cert i ficate, 2 015